I've been doing this for such a long time.
Live delivery is in.
Please give my best regards.
Please give my regards cheerfully.
May I ask you to do it?
Yes.
It's your first time, isn't it?
Senior citizen event.
Let's join forces.
GO! GO! GO!
Thank you very much.
On the contrary, thank you.
I like the angle of your legs when you crouch.
Oh, what the hell?
Oh, hi.
Good evening.
So, this week...
As you can see, my shift work is at the National Transportation Bureau.
It's been 15 years.
That's right.
I came here right after I was born.
So he's one or two years old.
That's why...
I have a lot going on this week.
First of all, I'd like to continue with the program.
I'd like to do some things on a case-by-case basis
I'd like to do a variety of things as the show progresses.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
First of all...
I'd like to write a letter to you.
There's a unique food shop in my hometown, right?
I wonder what it's called.
You know, ramen using local specialties.
I used to go there when I was a student.
I don't know if it's a chain or what, but it's called "Staddon's".
I don't know if it's a chain or what, but there's a restaurant called "Staddon".
I think that's where it originated.
Wow, that's amazing!
It's in a place called Kokubunji in Tokyo.
What's so great about that place?What's so great about that place?
The dormitory is amazing!
It's not half bad.
When I was a student, we all went there together.
There are often amazing dormitory restaurants.
If you eat a certain amount of great food, your name is posted on the menu.
If your name is posted there, you're a homeless person.
People in my hometown said, "Oh my God!
I was so impressed that I couldn't forget it.
Of course, I'm working in Yokohama now, so I didn't have a chance to go there very often.
But I got a letter from someone who said he had been there for a long time.
Thank you very much for your kind words.
The other day, I went to the place of Master's memory, Super Strong Style restaurant!
It's a stadone store near Kokubunji station!
That's right!
I wrote a song about Kokubunji at that time.
It was like this stadone song, and the content was very strong.
By the way, this is how it looks like, but I think the appearance of the restaurant has changed a lot.
It was not called "Stamina Restaurant" in the old days.
It didn't say "Stadone" on the menu.
It's a different name, a normal name with a more reddish look. The layout of the restaurant is like this.
I think the layout of the shop was like this... it was called "National Autonomy Shop", so it's probably still in its infancy...
Anyway... this Stadoorn was amazing.
I don't know about now, but back then, the name was on it...
Or two large bowls of sta-don or one large bowl of sta-don and one large bowl of ramen... In short, if you eat two large bowls, your name will be displayed in the restaurant.
You know, you go into a restaurant, and you see a lot of rice bowls piled up in front of the waiter, and you think, "What's this?
It's like this.
It's like a helmet. It's so big you could wear it like that.
And there was a lot of rice on it.
Wow!
Surprisingly, there are not many ingredients on top.
It's quite good!
It stirred up my spirit of challenge at the time.
And the taste, too... a little bit of garlic and some kind of meat...
I don't know...
It's like a ginger-yaki set meal with a raw egg on top, so the regular portion is really good.
But the large portion had a lot of rice.
I tried many times, but I never had even one large portion.
Is a regular portion also quite big?
But it's still good to eat.
But a large portion is probably...I think it's more than twice as big as a bowl of rice.
I think it's more than twice as big as a bowl of beef. It's like a special bowl of rice at a beef bowl restaurant.
This is the helmet... I see.
It was a great time, so all the young people went there to test their mettle.
The staff were a little bit mischievous, a little bit local, a little bit Benbenben.
At that time, it's really rude to say this now, but I was just giving them a rough time.
At the time, there were store clerks who looked a bit like those so-called "buzzers", you know?
He had a face a little like that one, and he had a perm.
I called him a "punch seal" on my own.
There's a "punch seal" here. I don't know if it's the ceiling or what, but it's the scariest thing I've ever seen.
I don't know if it's the ceiling or what, but it's the scariest thing I've ever seen... it looks so sleek!
Of course, if you leave something at a restaurant, you have to pay a certain amount of money for it.
If you eat it, it's really cheap, but if you leave it, you have to pay for it, and every time you leave it, you're going to the place where I punch a bunch of sealions.
And there was a small park near the restaurant.
I can't move!
Even though they were going through such a hard time, they would go back there. I just want to see the panther seals.
I love them. Yes, I loved Panchazarashi.
I used to say "PA" for short while putting it away. I was gradually saying Puncher Porcupine.
PA. I heard that PA had recently quit something. Like, "Really? I was like, "Seriously? What's the point of going? Like, "Wow.
Wow, I went to see PA. It was like I went all the way to see the PA.
Do you have that? That kind of unique local thing. It doesn't have to be Omori or something.
It didn't have to be Omori or anything, but something like, "This is only in my hometown. Only in your hometown?
Oh, but the shore of the Shinkansen platform at Nagoya Station, for example. There it is! Sumiyoshi! Sumiyoshi!
It's famous, isn't it? It's delicious, isn't it? Delicious.
It's not fair, is it? It's not fair. It's cheap. Cheap. No, really.
I asked someone in Nagoya, and he told me that there is now one on each platform of the Shinkansen, both up and down.
And there are also ones on the conventional lines. They say that the conventional lines are the most delicious.
I wonder.... Did Mr. Niimo say that? I think so.
You can find it at many stations. Yes, there are. They are very prosperous. The bridge side.
It's amazing. The Shinkansen is taking quite a bit of time again.
There used to be only one on the way down or something, right? There was only one.
So, when we were going back home, the platform for the Tokyo direction was not there, so we had to go there, even though we had a little time for the Shinkansen. So I thought, "I've got to go there.
I would go there, eat at a very high speed, and then go back again. He went like this, ate at a very high speed, and then went like this again.
I see. I see. That's how good it is.
Wow, it's good. It's delicious.
I guess the Nagoya area is a coastal area. When I think of udon, I think of Kishimae. There are many Kishimen.
Machida? Machida, but... I think there is something in Machida, too, right? Something like Stavina.
I think there might be, but there is a ramen restaurant I want to take my master to someday. In Machida? Ramen Evolution. Evolution? It's a salt ramen restaurant.
Evolution is exactly what it sounds like? It really evolves. It's an evolution.
Yes, but the chashu pork is chicken chashu pork, and it's really good!Yes, but the chashu pork is chicken chashu pork, and it is so delicious, the best salt ramen I have ever had.
Is there such a restaurant in your hometown? There was a ramen fanatic who did a monthly ranking of ramen restaurants he ate that month, and this one even made the list.
What! It's such a good ramen restaurant that it was in the top 5. I hope to see you at Ramen Evolution next time. Shio Ramen. I don't usually eat salt ramen at all. Really? I can't help it. It's so thick. It's very rich.
Sometimes I eat shio ramen. Shio ramen is really like that. It really brings out the flavor. It's all in that clear, clear flavor. No, that's right. The owner said he likes rock music, so there is hard rock music playing. It's really hard rock music. Like Metallica. Like Metallica.
Amazing. It's really delicious. Please try it all on top. There's "Zenmodate". The evolution of ramen. By the way, do you eat ramen here? Yes, I do. Yes, I do. Not at all. Soy sauce, for sure. But the seafood tonkotsu is the best. Seafood tonkotsu. Wow! It's delicious. I love it. Fish, all the fish is melted into it. I can't get enough of that feeling. Delicious. It's delicious.
Well, well, well. So, you know, we will continue to eat, because we are especially fond of food. Yes, we do. Please keep sending us your stories. Please keep sending us your stories.
That's all I have to say. Well then, let's see what's going on with the program. I think that's all for today. Okay, that's all for now. So, see you all tomorrow! See you tomorrow!
Okay, I'll go straight to Kiichi.
I like the Misudo mackerel the best.
It's good. Missed?
Miss Don's. Have you ever had it?
No, I have not.
It's really good.
Really?
It's light and super delicious.
Wow. Even sushi restaurants serve ramen now, right?
Yes, they do.
You can find it anywhere.
Seafood-based ramen is amazing. The soup stock.
Yes, it is.
It's amazing.
It's right away.
I like it.
Right away. Of dried bonito stock.
There's a restaurant that serves dried fish soup.
Looks delicious.
Hamahoshi.
I want to eat there.
Hamasei.
I see.
Yes!
Well, that's why I'm here.
Well, I really think about it every time.
A week really goes by fast, doesn't it?
It goes by so fast.
It's Friday in the blink of an eye.
It means my life is getting shorter and shorter.
It means I'm getting closer and closer to the end of my life.
In short...
Well, we're moving forward in the same amount of time.
No, no, no, no, no.No, no, no, no, no.
Scary!
Scary.
A little slower.
A lot.
Faster.
Sometimes a second goes by faster than you think.
It's true.
That's exactly what I mean.
So...
First of all, I'd like to write to you again.
Well, let's see...
By the way, let me tell you what day it is.
It's Friday, September 1st!
September at last!
Right?
What's September in English?
Octobar... Octobar October...
Octobar... yes, October...
September!
Yes!
I think...
Barrigatah had an achievement test the other day.
I saw it. I saw it.
He's amazing!
That's right.
It's the first time I lost.
I thought, "Are you serious?
I thought I'd go home and study.
I was so disappointed.
It's hard on the brain.
Thank you very much.
I think Kokun and the others are like this... naughty... but I think...
I have a feeling he can study better than I thought.
You know...
I think I can do it.
You can't do that.
You look like you could do it.
Well, as good as anyone can do.
There are a lot of people who can't even do as well as others.There are a lot of people who can't even do it as well as other people.
Especially the shrimpers.
That's right.
That 16th guy... Ganbadan...
That guy's bad.
He's bad...
He's all kinds of dangerous.
It's funny, isn't it?
He's funny, but...
But he's a little wary of the norm, even before his studies.
I'm in a lot of trouble.
Tomorrow is Saturday, September 2nd.
Tomorrow is of course Saturday, September 2nd, and it's Lottery Day!
Lottery
I see...
Lottery day.
Well, of course...
I think it's more like "let's buy lottery tickets.
The purpose is amazing!
There are so many lottery tickets that are not redeemed even if they win.
There are so many lottery tickets that are not redeemed and become time-barred.
What?
That means there are so many people who don't go to redeem their lottery tickets even if they win!
What a waste!
What's it to us?
It's not fair!
I wish I'd bought it because of that.
I guess a lot of people don't look at it and just leave it like it is.
What?
Is that so?
I heard about it before.
It was quite a lot of money.
It's like, "Oh, really?
I see.
That's why I asked you to buy more.
Tomorrow, September 2nd.
I'd like to have it replaced, even if it's only 300 yen.
Really.
I'd like to have it exchanged even if it's 100 yen or something.I'd like to have it exchanged, even if it's for $100 or something.
It's true, isn't it?
By the way, have you ever won a lottery like this?
Isn't that right, ice cream?
Yes, we have ice cream.
GariGari lottery
Like winning.
I haven't won anything like that yet in my life.
I used to eat chestnuts.
No, there was an ice cream called "sato-no-kuri".
I've never heard of it.
I don't think anyone knows about it.
It was on sale temporarily when I was in high school.
It was a big hit with my soccer team.
We were like, "Let's eat chestnuts from the village!
I was like, "I got it!
Vanilla ice cream?
Yes.
It's vanilla ice cream with a little chestnut chocolate coating.
It's delicious.
Chestnut buns.
I can't remember the name of the company that makes chestnuts.
If I saw it now, I'd wish they'd reissue it.
That's about right.
Maybe there's someone here who's had sato no kuri.
I don't know...
I'm sure they do now.
When I was in high school
I had them!
Do they still sell them?
Do you sell it somewhere?
Do you sell it?
I wonder if they still sell them.
I guess they don't sell them.
I wonder if they're still around.
Chestnuts in the village. It was a masterpiece.
And it comes with a prize.
It's a lucky one.
I won 7 times.
But I've probably eaten over 300 of them.
So the probability is pretty low.Probability or not, it's pretty low.
What do you have?
I used to go to a dagashi shop in my neighborhood when I was in junior high.
When you open it, it's like a soccer ball Ramune.
I won 100 yen once.
I've been to this place, and I've been to these dagashi parlors.
Fighting animals.
It's like being a kid in the Showa period.
You know, back in the day, if we'd stayed like that...
We'd all have to face each other.
You're so tough.
I want them to grow up.
You don't do this side of the business?
I'm good at this too.
I like games.
I often stream games.
Wow...
What are you, a man who can do anything?
I can do anything.
That's awesome!
You can do this.
You kill beasts, don't you?
I didn't kill any beasts.
Oh, my God, that's amazing.
That's great.
I can do this.
You can't do this.
Like this.
Yes!
Not yet.
This one... is okay.
Like a lottery ticket.
I don't know.
I've won a lot.
It's amazing, isn't it?
You know what?
It's like the last show.
Last show.
Last one show.Last One Show
The last one, right?
It's the last one.
You know...
Those figures were amazing.
That was amazing!
Well, well, well... I hope you all enjoy it.
Maybe I'm right.
That's right.
Maybe it's too much trouble to check.
If you buy a lot, you'll have to ask for it every week.
It's faster to ask for help.
Can I ask him to check it for me?
If you don't buy, you don't win.
That's why I buy lottery tickets.
Me, too.
It's not a lottery.
When I used to go to horse races...
I'd buy tickets...
Until there's a hole in it.
Until there was a hole in it.
Why can't I win this one?
I used to throw them.
Shhh...
It's not going in the trash.
There's no way it's going in the trash.
Well, well, well...
Let's hear from you.
Let's go.
Oh, that's nice.
The season is...
There may be another one.
It's chilled Chinese noodles.
It's delicious.
You like it?
I don't have anything against chilled noodles.
I have nothing against chilled noodles.
But you've got Mr. Cucumber in there.
Cucumbers and chilled noodles don't go well together.
Ah, cucumbers!Ah, cucumbers!
I told you, no cucumber.
Ask for it.
No cucumber, please.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
I feel like the cucumber is telling me not to eat it if that's the case.
Cucumbers!
What are you looking at?
It's like...
Like, "Oh, no, you...
Okay, then.
I'll turn it down at Tutu-shin.
I haven't eaten chilled Chinese food at all in recent years.
Oh...
On the contrary, cucumber, ham and tomatoes are enough for chilled Chinese noodles.
That's right.
Why is cucumber in there?
I wonder very much.
Well, well, well...
Chilled Chinese noodles.
May I?
Chilled Chinese noodles company
Hachioji no Owl-kun
Very nice!
It's chilled Chinese food in the city.
There's a great street Chinese restaurant in Hachioji called Chitose.
There's a nice street Chinese restaurant called Chitose in Hachioji.
Nice street Chinese.
Is it?
Se-no.
Looks delicious!
Cucumber and ham.
Ham and Kamaboko!
I wonder if it's cucumber, ham, and ham and kamaboko.
Cucumber is definitely not good for coloring!
The green color is chilled Chinese noodles.
Lettuce would be good too.
Green
No...
Edamame.Edamame.
Sounds good.
Yes, sir.
Wow, this is amazing.
Looks delicious.
We just had dinner.
It's true, isn't it?
Can you eat this much?
I can.
Yes, you can.
Yes, and later...
Let's see...
Um...
The ballet is this way, not that way.
Yes, yes, this one.
I think all three of us are remembering the wrong thing.
Some boys play ballet, but there are a lot of girls when you meet them.
I have an image of that.
I've never played ballet.
I've never done it.
Oh?
And when we talked about ballet...
Yes.
Ms. Shuilene from Mishima City, Shizuoka Prefecture.
Well... the guest at the ballet class was... a boy.
He's a boy, but he said he got a lot of Valentine's Day chocolates at the ballet school because it's all girls.
I'm sure he'll get some.
He said that.
He did say that.
Yes, I did.
And when I heard that, I said, "Okay, I'll do ballet, too.
I heard he said that.
I don't remember.
I'm sure I said so, because I always get involved in such a conversation.
But if I were to do ballet, I imagine it would be like this.
Oh!
This...
Ha-ha-ha!
Cool!Ah cool!
That looks like it's going to be unexpectedly short.
Hey, that's nice.
You're right. Male ballet dudes are awesome.
I like it.
Let's do it all like this.
Yes, on the contrary.
Like this.
There are male ballet dancers like this, tied up like this.
It's a little skate-like.
Yes, that's true.
It's cool.
It's like figure skating.
Yes, it is.
Like Yuzuru Hanyu or the master.
I guess so.
Ha-ha-ha.
I'm not in the same category as Yuzuru Hanyu.
I don't think we'd have anything to say to each other if I talked to him directly.
Maybe.
Various things.
No, but it's good.
It's nice.
It's cool.
And also, there's a picture...
Yes...
Mr. Shiroko and the lady who plays Shibu Miyato who often send me pictures these days.
Thank you very much!
The other day... when we had another guest...
Yes...
A person who can draw a portrait in 10 seconds.
Amazing.
And Mr. Shirokane is good at drawing too.
Yes?
He tried it... in 10 seconds.
10 seconds each.
10 seconds each.10 seconds per person
Ten seconds each.
Well, what a surprise...
All the members of the TV crew in the museum drew this picture.
What?
This is...
Yum!
Oh, wow!
You've captured the characteristics so well!
It's amazing.
Well, you know, for me, maybe...
I think I can draw it in 10 seconds.
Ha-ha-ha.
In terms of parts...
This...
It's amazing, isn't it?
Amazing.
Even the bedrock valley looks the same.
They look exactly the same.
Right?
Everyone can see it.
Shibuya looks just like him
The national fortunes look the same.
Ha-ha-ha-ha...
What is it?
It's like...
It's just like him.
huh?
How many seconds did it take you to draw this?
That's why...
This...
This one...
This one
But
But about 30 seconds
I think it was about 30 secondsI think it was like 30 seconds.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
With me.
I'm so embarrassed.
It wasn't me.
With Eren from the advancing giants.
Master...
I can't believe I drew that.
No way!
No, no, no, no...
But you also say in your book that it was difficult...
And, you know, China... well, of course you know what China is, what China does...
It's not easy to draw...
I've barely been to China before... and I've had a lot of trouble there...
I've never been to China... but I'd like to go there... because it's the origin of Japanese culture... or, yes... the origin of everything...
It's where it all started.
The father was going to go to a great place... to watch an anime, Ghibli, and Chihiro...
Boo-hoo!
Boo-boo!
It's not too much, it's in China, Taiwan, nine times...
Taiwan, nine times... Hong Kong, that place... that's the model, right?
I've always wanted to go to China.
Mr. Shackelford, we're going to start with an ad for Yokohama City.
I went to a place called Tonkoton in China.
I heard there's a desert there, so it's easy to get around.
I don't know how easy it is or how long it takes, but it's like this.
It's like this...
It's really a desert, isn't it? The air of sand is like a slide...
Oh, it's so cool!
I want to climb up Mt. Suna, it must be really hard.
It's a big mountain
There's the Tottori Sand Dunes... where you walk through the desert until you get to the ocean...
It was tough... the sand took my feet and I couldn't go forward at all... and I think I sank.
By the way... that's the site where they store the Giant Buddha.
I heard there's a big horror hole in the ruins that holds the Big Buddha.
It's amazing... a human being like this.
There's a big statue of the Great Buddha in the middle of this big hole, isn't there?
What do you see?
It says it's about 3 times bigger than the Big Buddha of Kamakura.
That's huge... and the food is also very generous...That's huge... and that food is also very exuberant.
8... a whole roasted leg of lamb... star... this part... maybe the leg...
I've never heard of roasting a whole leg.
I can still imagine a pig's foot.
I can still imagine it.
It's like this. A foot. Wow, it's bigger than I thought.
but I'm sure it's delicious grilled slowly.
Lamb is delicious, isn't it? Lamb is delicious.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes...
By the way...
Everyone has a birthday... on the 1/365th or 1/366th of a month.
It's August now, isn't it?
August, right?
Kazomi, the day after tomorrow, the day after tomorrow, your birthday
Yes, that's right, that's right I'll have a birthday in May
That's the closest to January. - That's March.
That means I'm closest to August?
So you're celebrating me today?
A little earlier?
A little while ago?
By the way, you don't know what that means, do you?
You're celebrating a birthday.
Why would it be a little while ago?
You're supposed to meet someone close.
What's the national holiday, by the way?
What month?
The 20th of March.
I see.
That would make it...
That's about five months ago.
It's the day before his debut in the big trunk.
Yes, that's right.
I guess...
Every month on this show, the staff gives a gift to Ebisu Sha, and they probably thought they'd give it to her here, but she never shows up, so...
Tokyo Cafe Distance
Tokyo Cafe Distance... I don't want to keep working part-time, like an idiot.
Finally...
Is this it?
Oh!
Oh, this way.Oh, over here.
Hamin received a Koku Happi Birthday Devil's Charge!
Wow, thank you so much!
He said this bag was left here.
Tonkatsu?
Maisen!
A pork cutlet as a present?
No, no, no, I'm flattered.
I'm surprised. It's a pork cutlet.
I thought it was a maisen. It's a good sandwich, isn't it? It's delicious.
It wasn't this one. I wonder why they put it in the back. Ah! There it is! Something like that!
I'm so happy!
Tattler!
A birthday present!
Yes, it didn't look anything like it.
Yeah, I know. I regretted it after I said it.
Here you go. Thank you very much.
What the hell is this?
Feri... feri...
I give up. I give up.
I'll open it. Say "Felli." You're very bold.
I rotated it.
I spun it.
Mr. Devilch, I wish you a very happy birthday.
Happy birthday to you, Mr. Devilch, from the Devilchannel.
What?
What? I can't read English.
It says "channel." It says "channel." Let's open it up. Channel, that channel?
Channel? Channel New York? Channel glue?
Glue? Channel glue? It's in there like this. It's in there. It's in there.
It's New York glue.
I'm glad. I like New York glue.
I'm a New York lumber hobbyist. - Wow, I'm glad you know that. Thank you.
Wow, I'll put it in today.
I would've laughed if it was Chanel.
I heard they do Chanel's groove, too.
Chanel's logo is on the flippers.
I'm curious.
They're doing it piece by piece.
It's like, "This is expensive.
What is that? Is there a scent?What is it? Does it have a scent?
Go ahead.
It smells good.
Bath salts shouldn't smell so bad.
It says something about it.
Maybe it smells a little nice.
Eutensel.
What are you talking about?
It's not easy.
It's not French, is it?
French?
You too, Mr. Kahikaho.
With the launch of Black Cloud this year, plus HAPPY BAR...
I have a chance to be on the next level.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Bertie and Mr. Hyakushiki
Congratulations to Kurokumo and congratulations on the 5 month delay!
Thank you very much!
Smells great!
It's amazing.
It's so nice!
So...
We're almost done with the live streaming.
It's almost time for the live broadcast to end.
Since we're here...
Black Cloud will be here in about 15 years.
Probably
Around the lunar eclipse
I'll probably be 30 years old.
When I'm 30 years old.
I don't know if it's coming.
I don't know.
For those who are watching.
Yeah, I know.
There's nothing here.
It's fine.
I heard about it yesterday.
Okay, then.
Let's show everyone the thunder of the black clouds.
Last one.
Shall we take it then?Well, I guess I'll take it.
Gentlemen.
Thundering black clouds.
It's a black cloud.
Here you go.
Congratulations.
Thank you for watching.
a batch of Raptor Yes, and that's why I have a cheap situation 0
Azarro book, well, I don't know what's going on.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea to have a new one, but I'm sure it's a good idea to have a new one.
a
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I understand.
Well, well, well, well...
So, how about Amagasin next week?
8:00 p.m.!
So, see you next week!
Thank you very much for your time today!